0 O O Provisioning
0 O O of
0 O O different
0 O O types
0 O O of
0 O O network
0 O O speeds
0 O O for
0 O O multiple
0 O O clients

0 O O We
0 O O co-
0 O O ordinate
0 O O with
0 O O various
0 O O ops
0 O O and
0 O O field
0 O O engineers
0 O O to
0 O O do
0 O O the
0 O O connections
0 O O at
0 O O the
0 O O physical
0 O O level

0 O U-CARDINAL 2
0 O O Organisation
0 O B-ORG QuadGen
0 O I-ORG Wireless
0 O I-ORG Engineering
0 O I-ORG Services
0 O I-ORG Pvt

0 O L-ORG Ltd.
0 O U-PERSON Bangalore

0 O O Ltd.
0 O U-PERSON Manipal

0 O O Position
0 O O Intern
0 O O Experience
0 O B-DATE 1
0 O L-DATE year
0 O O Exposure

0 O U-GPE Module
0 O O coding
0 O O and
0 O O verification
0 O O using
0 O U-GPE Verilog
0 O O HDL

0 O U-PERSON Worked
0 O O on
0 O O Linux
0 O O O.S.

0 O B-ORG Understanding
0 O I-ORG of
0 O L-ORG SPI
0 O O I2C
0 O O protocols

0 O O Compilation
0 O O using
0 O O Altera
0 O O Quartus

0 O O Simulation
0 O O using
0 O B-ORG ModelSim

0 O B-PERSON Verilog
0 O L-PERSON HDL

0 O U-PERSON Knowledge
0 O O of
0 O U-ORG RTL
0 O O coding
0 O U-ORG FSM
0 O O based
0 O O designs

0 O B-ORG Understanding
0 O I-ORG of
0 O L-ORG UART
0 O U-ORG AMBA
0 O O protocol

0 O O Platforms
0 O U-ORG Microsoft
0 O O office
0 O U-ORG Libreoffice

1 O O It
1 O O involves
1 O O troubleshooting
1 O O and
1 O O resolving
1 O O workflow
1 O O errors
1 O O and
1 O O provisioning
1 O O user
1 O O access

1 O O I
1 O O perform
1 O O identity
1 O O and
1 O O access
1 O O management
1 O O activities
1 O O updating
1 O O existing
1 O O access
1 O O and
1 O O provisioning
1 O O workflows
1 O O manage
1 O O operations
1 O O within
1 O O the
1 O U-ORG IAM
1 O O environment

1 O O Currently
1 O O I
1 O O 'm
1 O O working
1 O O on
1 O O automating
1 O O the
1 O O work
1 O O flow
1 O O of
1 O O Security
1 O O Intelligence
1 O O and
1 O O Response
1 O O Team
1 O O with
1 O O Phantom
1 O O and
1 O O Python
1 O O scripting

1 O O I
1 O O 'm
1 O O trained
1 O O in
1 O U-GPE Python
1 O U-GPE Solaris
1 O O administration
1 O U-PERSON Java
1 O O and
1 O U-PERSON PLSQL

1 O O I
1 O O 'm
1 O O able
1 O O to
1 O O handle
1 O O multiple
1 O O tasks
1 O O and
1 O O work
1 O O as
1 O O a
1 O O team
1 O O Member

1 O O I
1 O O 'm
1 O O committed
1 O O goal
1 O O oriented
1 O O has
1 O O zeal
1 O O to
1 O O learn
1 O O new
1 O O things
1 O O technologies

1 O O I
1 O O possess
1 O O good
1 O O problem
1 O O solving
1 O O interpersonal
1 O O skills
1 O O good
1 O O communication
1 O O skills
1 O O and
1 O O team
1 O O spirit

1 O O WORK
1 O B-ORG EXPERIENCE
1 - I-ORG Technology
1 - L-ORG Analyst
1 O O Infosys
1 O O Limited
1 O O Chandigarh
1 O B-ORG Chandigarh
1 O B-DATE October
1 O L-DATE 2013
1 O O to
1 O B-ORG Present
1 O I-ORG A.
1 O I-ORG Change
1 O L-ORG Management
1 O O Installing
1 O O and
1 O O upgrading
1 O U-ORG RT
1 O O and
1 O O RTIR
1 O O for
1 O O improved
1 O O request
1 O O handling
1 O O with
1 O U-PERSON MySQL
1 O O database

1 O B-PERSON B.
1 O I-PERSON Python
1 O L-PERSON Automation
1 O O Automating
1 O O various
1 O O use
1 O O cases
1 O O for
1 O B-ORG the
1 O I-ORG Security
1 O I-ORG Intelligence
1 O I-ORG and
1 O I-ORG Response
1 O L-ORG Team
1 O O using
1 O B-ORG Python
1 O O scripting
1 O O and
1 O O Phantom
1 O O tool
1 O O integrating
1 O O it
1 O O with
1 O O various
1 O O tools
1 O O i.e.
1 O U-ORG Splunk
1 O B-PERSON Request
1 O L-PERSON Tracker
1 O O for
1 O O Incident
1 O O Response
1 O O RTIR
1 O U-PERSON Remedy
1 O O etc

1 O U-PERSON Below
1 O O are
1 O O the
1 O O use
1 O O cases
1 O O details
1 O O Use
1 O O Cases
1 O O Description
1 O O Proxy
1 O O Blocks
1 O O Enable
1 O O the
1 O O ability
1 O O to
1 O O block
1 O O domains
1 O O and
1 O O URLs
1 O O automatically
1 O O on
1 O U-PERSON Bluecoat
1 O O proxies
1 O O using
1 O O a
1 O O list
1 O O maintained
1 O O in
1 O O SPLUNK
1 O B-GPE Palo
1 O I-GPE Alto
1 O L-GPE Blocks
1 O O Enable
1 O O the
1 O O ability
1 O O to
1 O O block
1 O O domains
1 O O and
1 O O URLs
1 O O automatically
1 O O on
1 O B-GPE Palo
1 O L-GPE Alto
1 O O proxies
1 O O using
1 O O a
1 O O list
1 O O maintained
1 O O in
1 O O SPLUNK
1 O B-PERSON Threat
1 O I-PERSON Intel
1 O L-PERSON Email
1 O O feed
1 O O ingestion
1 O O Take
1 O O emails
1 O O from
1 O O an
1 O O external
1 O O distribution
1 O O group
1 O O and
1 O O parse
1 O O the
1 O O emails
1 O O for
1 O O IOCs
1 O B-ORG Email
1 O I-ORG Eradication
1 O O When
1 O O a
1 O O Malicious
1 O O email
1 O O has
1 O O been
1 O O detected
1 O O as
1 O O being
1 O O received
1 O O in
1 O B-ORG the
1 O I-ORG Microsoft
1 O L-ORG Exchange
1 O O email
1 O O system
1 O O perform
1 O O eradication
1 O O steps
1 O O to
1 O O remove
1 O O the
1 O O email
1 O O from
1 O O the
1 O O email
1 O O messaging
1 O O platform
1 O B-PERSON Email
1 O L-PERSON Quarantine
1 O O Email
1 O O addresses
1 O O alerted
1 O O as
1 O O malicious
1 O O need
1 O O to
1 O O be
1 O O added
1 O O to
1 O O a
1 O O quarantine
1 O O list
1 O O Malware
1 O U-PERSON Response
1 O O When
1 O O malware
1 O O is
1 O O detected
1 O O by
1 O O alert
1 O O or
1 O O scanning
1 O O initiate
1 O O containment
1 O O procedures
1 O O for
1 O O the
1 O O affected
1 O O device
1 O O in
1 O O question
1 O B-ORG Unapproved
1 O L-ORG Devices
1 O O https://www.indeed.com/r/Vikas-Singh/8644db42854c4f6a?isid=rex-download&ikw=download-top&co=IN
1 O O When
1 O O alerts
1 O O for
1 O B-ORG Unapproved
1 O L-ORG Devices
1 O O equipment
1 O O that
1 O O is
1 O O not
1 O O in
1 O U-ORG Organization
1 O O asset
1 O O inventory
1 O O is
1 O O triggered
1 O O containment
1 O O needs
1 O O to
1 O O occur
1 O O for
1 O O the
1 O O device
1 O O in
1 O O question
1 O O IOC
1 O O Detect
1 O O and
1 O U-GPE Scanning
1 O O using
1 O U-PERSON Tanium
1 O O and
1 O O Fireeye
1 O O HX
1 O O When
1 O B-ORG Indicators
1 O I-ORG of
1 O L-ORG Compromise
1 O O IOC
1 O O are
1 O O received
1 O O from
1 O O various
1 O O sources
1 O O threat
1 O O intel
1 O O feeds
1 O O exploded
1 O O malware
1 O O the
1 O O network
1 O O environment
1 O O needs
1 O O to
1 O O be
1 O O scanned
1 O O for
1 O O any
1 O O of
1 O O the
1 O O indicators
1 O O of
1 O O compromise
1 O O provided

1 O O Also
1 O O making
1 O O sure
1 O O access
1 O O is
1 O O disabled
1 O O on
1 O O the
1 O O user
1 O O departure
1 O O date
1 O O and
1 O O cleaning
1 O O up
1 O O of
1 O O all
1 O O the
1 O O access

1 O O Reviewing
1 O O access
1 O O periodically
1 O O and
1 O O updating
1 O O it
1 O O accordingly

1 O B-PERSON B.
1 O L-PERSON Access
1 O O management
1 O O This
1 O O involves
1 O O provisioning
1 O O de
1 O O provisioning
1 O O access
1 O O to
1 O O users
1 O O across
1 O U-CARDINAL 300
1 O O applications
1 O O using
1 O O various
1 O O global
1 O O and
1 O O in
1 O O house
1 O O tools
1 O O like
1 O O RSA
1 O O security
1 O O console
1 O U-ORG SAP
1 O B-ORG Identity
1 O L-ORG IIQ
1 O O etc

1 O O across
1 O O multiple
1 O O platforms
1 O O like
1 O U-ORG UNIX
1 O U-ORG Database
1 O O and
1 O O application
1 O O front
1 O O end

1 O O Making
1 O O sure
1 O O standard
1 O O operative
1 O O procedures
1 O U-ORG SOP
1 O O are
1 O O followed
1 O O validation
1 O O checks
1 O O are
1 O O completed
1 O O and
1 O O appropriate
1 O O approvals
1 O O are
1 O O gathered
1 O O before
1 O O access
1 O O is
1 O O granted

1 O O Monitoring
1 O O and
1 O O tracking
1 O O the
1 O O corrective
1 O O actions
1 O O are
1 O O taken
1 O O within
1 O O defined
1 O O timeframe

1 O O Doing
1 O O RCA
1 O O on
1 O O major
1 O O issues
1 O O Developing
1 O O Service
1 O O Improvement
1 O O Plan
1 O U-ORG SIP
1 O O and
1 O O Process
1 O O Improvement
1 O O Plan
1 O U-ORG PIP
1 O O based
1 O O on
1 O O the
1 O O QAP
1 O O analysis
1 O O D.
1 O O Risk
1 O O Management
1 O O Identifying
1 O O risk
1 O O areas
1 O O through
1 O U-DATE daily
1 O O and
1 O O periodic
1 O O report
1 O B-ORG E.g.
1 O L-ORG Segregation
1 O O of
1 O O duties
1 O O violation
1 O O SOD
1 O O report
1 O O Active
1 O O directory
1 O O infraction
1 O O report
1 O O etc

1 O O Working
1 O O with
1 O O various
1 O O teams
1 O O to
1 O O mitigate
1 O O the
1 O O violations

1 O O Assisting
1 O O auditors
1 O O by
1 O O provide
1 O O details
1 O O and
1 O O justification
1 O O on
1 O O audit
1 O O samples

1 O O E.
1 O O Client
1 O O Coordination
1 O O Coordinating
1 O O with
1 O O client
1 O U-DATE daily
1 O U-DATE weekly
1 O O for
1 O O the
1 O O operations
1 O O issues
1 O O and
1 O O feedback
1 O O with
1 O O the
1 O O respective
1 O O reports
1 O O prepared

2 O B-PERSON Puneeth
2 O L-PERSON R
2 B-Designation B-ORG Escalation
2 L-Designation I-ORG Specialist
2 O I-ORG HiPower
2 O I-ORG Support
2 O L-ORG Centre
2 O O Bengaluru
2 O B-PERSON Karnataka
2 O L-PERSON Email
2 O O me
2 O O on
2 O O Indeed
2 O O indeed.com/r/Puneeth-R/bc332220e733906d
2 O O To
2 O O be
2 O O an
2 O O asset
2 O O to
2 O O my
2 O O organization
2 O O by
2 O O utilizing
2 O O the
2 O O recent
2 O O improving
2 O O trends
2 O O and
2 O O make
2 O O optimum
2 O O use
2 O O of
2 O O the
2 O O available
2 O O resources
2 O O for
2 O O the
2 O O success
2 O O of
2 O O the
2 O O company

2 O O More
2 O O importantly
2 O O working
2 O O harmoniously
2 O O in
2 O O a
2 O O team
2 O O to
2 O O bring
2 O O forth
2 O O the
2 O O best
2 O O from
2 O O self
2 O O and
2 O O everyone

2 O O Escalating
2 O O tickets
2 O O to
2 O O clients
2 O B-ORG Creating
2 O L-ORG Inquiries
2 O O regarding
2 O O the
2 O O process
2 O O to
2 O O receive
2 O O update
2 O O from
2 O U-ORG Clients
2 O O Providing
2 O O feedback
2 O O to
2 O O Agents
2 O O regarding
2 O O Clients
2 O O Escalations
2 O O and
2 O O internal
2 O O invalid
2 O U-ORG Escalations

2 O O Team
2 O O handling
2 O O Mentor

2 O B-PERSON Monitoring
2 O L-PERSON Queue
2 O O Allocating
2 O O Agents
2 O O to
2 O O different
2 O O queues
2 O B-ORG Preparing
2 O L-ORG Reports
2 O U-ORG Process
2 O O improvements
2 O O initiatives

2 O O Taking
2 O O operations
2 O O training
2 O O sessions
2 O O on
2 O U-PRODUCT Gameplay
2 O U-ORG DSAT
2 O O reviews
2 O U-ORG Quality
2 O U-ORG FTR
2 O O and
2 O U-ORG Tickets
2 O O handling

2 O B-ORG Maintaining
2 O L-ORG amp
2 O O ensuring
2 O O stringent
2 O O adherence
2 O O to
2 O O quality
2 O O standards
2 O O identifying
2 O O gaps
2 O O and
2 O O opportunities
2 O O by
2 O O live
2 O O assistance

2 O O Handled
2 O O OJT
2 O O and
2 O B-ORG Tenured
2 O L-ORG Team

2 O O Handling
2 O O Supervisor
2 O O tickets
2 O U-PERSON Lead
2 O O compensations
2 O O and
2 O U-ORG Audits

2 O B-PERSON Sales
2 O L-PERSON Associate
2 O O in
2 O U-GPE Convergys
2 O U-ORG AT&T
2 O B-DATE January
2 O L-DATE 2014
2 O O to
2 O B-DATE May
2 O L-DATE 2015
2 O O Client
2 O O AT&amp;T
2 O B-ORG Roles
2 O L-ORG amp
2 O O Responsibilities

2 O B-PERSON Making
2 O L-PERSON Calls
2 O O to
2 O O customers
2 O O in
2 O O case
2 O O of
2 O O lead
2 O O generations

2 O O Process
2 O O Executive
2 O O Operations
2 O O in
2 O U-GPE Infosys
2 O O Cisco
2 O B-DATE August
2 O I-DATE 2012
2 O I-DATE to
2 O I-DATE November
2 O L-DATE 2013
2 O O Client
2 O B-PERSON Cisco
2 O O https://www.indeed.com/r/Puneeth-R/bc332220e733906d?isid=rex-download&ikw=download-top&co=IN
2 O O Contd

2 O B-ORG Roles
2 O L-ORG amp
2 O O Responsibilities

2 O B-ORG Assisting
2 O L-ORG Clients
2 O O over
2 O U-PERSON Email
2 O O and
2 O O Phone
2 O O regarding
2 O O Billing
2 O O discrepancies
2 O O and
2 O B-ORG Order
2 O L-ORG Management

2 O O CRM
2 O O tool
2 O O experience
2 O O in
2 O U-GPE Supporting
2 O O and
2 O O Reports
2 O O generation

2 O B-ORG Customer
2 O I-ORG Relations
2 O L-ORG Officer
2 O O in
2 O O HGS
2 O B-DATE December
2 O I-DATE 2011
2 O I-DATE to
2 O I-DATE July
2 O L-DATE 2012
2 O O Client
2 O O MTS

2 O O Making
2 O O calls
2 O O to
2 O O customers
2 O O to
2 O O review
2 O O customer
2 O O satisfaction
2 O O and
2 O O upselling

2 O B-PERSON Handled
2 O L-PERSON Escalations
2 O O from
2 O U-ORG Customers

2 O O Taking
2 O O Calls
2 O O to
2 O O address
2 O B-ORG Customers
2 - L-ORG Inquiries

2 - U-ORG EDUCATION
2 - O B.E
2 - B-ORG PES
2 - I-ORG College
2 O I-ORG of
2 O L-ORG Engineering
2 O O Mandya
2 O O Karnataka

3 O U-PERSON Sameer
3 O O More
3 O U-GPE Mumbai
3 O B-ORG Maharashtra
3 O L-ORG Email
3 O O me
3 O O on
3 O O Indeed
3 O O indeed.com/r/Sameer-More/183ccba2cb00a02a
3 O O Looking
3 O O for
3 O O opportunity
3 O O to
3 O O explore
3 O O my
3 O O skills
3 O O and
3 O O become
3 O B-ORG a
3 O I-ORG Professional
3 O I-ORG in
3 O L-ORG Industry

3 O O An
3 O O opportunity
3 O O that
3 O O gives
3 O O platform
3 O O good
3 O O working
3 O O environment
3 O O to
3 O O put
3 O B-PERCENT 100
3 O L-PERCENT %
3 O O efforts
3 O O for
3 O O an
3 O O organization
3 O O and
3 O O grow
3 O O with
3 O O an
3 O O organization
3 O O by
3 O O coordinating
3 O O with
3 O O the
3 O O seniors

3 O O WORK
3 O O EXPERIENCE
3 B-Designation O Assistant
3 I-Designation O Manager
3 L-Designation O Sales
3 O B-ORG Kotak
3 O I-ORG Mahindra
3 O L-ORG Bank
3 O O Mumbai
3 O U-ORG Maharashtra
3 O B-DATE February
3 O L-DATE 2018
3 O O to
3 O B-ORG Present
3 O L-ORG Sales
3 O O Marketing
3 O O EDUCATION
3 U-Degree B-ORG HSC
3 "B-College Name" U-GPE Mumbai
3 "L-College Name" O university
3 O U-GPE Mumbai
3 O U-ORG Maharashtra
3 O U-DATE 2012
3 O O to
3 O O 2013
3 U-Degree O SSC
3 O U-ORG Maharashtra
3 O O state
3 O O board
3 O U-DATE 2008
3 O O to
3 O U-DATE 2009
3 U-Degree B-ORG B.Com
3 O I-ORG Mumbai
3 O L-ORG University
3 O O ADDITIONAL
3 O O INFORMATION

3 O U-PERSON Honesty

3 O O Team
3 O O player

3 O O Punctuality

3 O O Listening

3 O O Patience

3 O O Flexible
3 O O for
3 O O working
3 O O in
3 O O any
3 O O situation

3 O O Self
3 O O -discipline
3 O O https://www.indeed.com/r/Sameer-More/183ccba2cb00a02a?isid=rex-download&ikw=download-top&co=IN

4 O O Aman
4 O O Panfeyy
4 B-Designation O Sales
4 L-Designation O Manager
4 O U-GPE Mumbai
4 O U-ORG Maharashtra
4 O U-ORG Maharashtra
4 O O Email
4 O O me
4 O O on
4 O O Indeed
4 O O indeed.com
4 O O r
4 O O Aman-
4 O O Panfeyy/1faf9b095409a61f
4 O O Build
4 O O a
4 O O full
4 O O scale
4 O O sales
4 O O operation
4 O O from
4 O O the
4 O O ground
4 O O up
4 O O duties
4 O O include
4 O O establishing
4 O O database
4 O O systems
4 O O recruitment
4 O O of
4 O B-ORG Sales
4 O L-ORG Executive
4 O O and
4 O O developing
4 O O sales
4 O O and
4 O O marketing
4 O O strategies
4 O O Passion
4 O O Intigrity
4 O U-ORG Positive
4 O O leadership
4 O O quality
4 O O WORK
4 O O EXPERIENCE
4 B-Designation O Sales
4 L-Designation O Manager
4 O O Jaycee
4 O O Construction
4 O B-DATE June
4 O I-DATE 2017
4 O L-DATE to
4 O B-DATE January
4 O L-DATE 2018
4 O O Handling
4 O O Customer
4 O O database
4 O O and
4 O O looking
4 O O after
4 O O customer
4 O O relationship
4 O O management
4 O O and
4 O O generating
4 O O a
4 O O leads
4 O O of
4 O O interested
4 O O investor
4 O O in
4 O O real
4 O O estate
4 O O market

4 B-Designation O Sales
4 L-Designation O Manager
4 O B-PERSON Shardha
4 O L-PERSON Motors
4 O B-DATE June
4 O I-DATE 2015
4 O I-DATE to
4 O I-DATE April
4 O L-DATE 2017
4 O O Managing
4 O O the
4 O O team
4 O O of
4 O O sales
4 O O executive
4 O O to
4 O O meetthe
4 O O target
4 O O and
4 O O implementing
4 O O new
4 O O advertising
4 O O strategy
4 O O to
4 O O boost
4 O O automobile
4 O O sale

4 O O And
4 O O maintaining
4 O O customer
4 O O database
4 B-Designation O Sales
4 I-Designation O team
4 L-Designation O leader
4 O U-CARDINAL One
4 O O stop
4 O O retail
4 O O ltd
4 O B-DATE June
4 O L-DATE 2013
4 O O to
4 O B-DATE May
4 O L-DATE 2015
4 O O Managing
4 O O the
4 O O team
4 O O of
4 O O representatives
4 O O and
4 O O ensuring
4 O O to
4 O O meet
4 O O sales
4 O O target

4 O O Generating
4 O O leads
4 O O of
4 O O potential
4 O O customer
4 O O along
4 O O with
4 O U-DATE daily
4 O O reports
4 O O and
4 O O analysis
4 O O EDUCATION
4 B-Degree O B
4 I-Degree O S.C
4 I-Degree O in
4 L-Degree B-ORG Commerce
4 "B-College Name" O University
4 "L-College Name" O technology
4 O U-GPE Mumbai
4 O U-ORG Maharashtra
4 O U-DATE 2016
4 U-Degree O H.s.c
4 O O https://www.indeed.com/r/Aman-Panfeyy/1faf9b095409a61f?isid=rex-download&ikw=download-top&co=IN
4 O O https://www.indeed.com/r/Aman-Panfeyy/1faf9b095409a61f?isid=rex-download&ikw=download-top&co=IN
4 - O junior
4 - O college
4 O U-DATE 2012
4 O O SKILLS
4 O U-ORG DATABASE
4 O B-DATE 2
4 O L-DATE years
4 O U-ORG CRM
4 O B-DATE Less
4 O I-DATE than
4 O I-DATE 1
4 O L-DATE year
4 O O CUSTOMER
4 O O RELATIONSHIP
4 O O MANAGEMENT
4 O O Less
4 O O than
4 O O 1
4 O O year
4 O B-ORG MICROSOFT
4 O L-ORG OFFICE
4 O O Less
4 O O than
4 O O 1
4 O O year
4 O B-ORG MS
4 O L-ORG OFFICE
4 O O Less
4 O O than
4 O O 1
4 O O year
4 O O ADDITIONAL
4 O O INFORMATION
4 O O SKILLS
4 O U-PERSON Customer
4 O O handling
4 O O Providing
4 O O high
4 O O end
4 O O customer
4 O O experience
4 O O to
4 O O ensure
4 O O customer
4 O O skills
4 O O satisfaction
4 O O and
4 O O boost
4 O O sale
4 O B-PERSON Computer
4 O L-PERSON Knowledge
4 O O Good
4 O O with
4 O U-ORG Microsoft
4 O O office
4 O O and
4 O O installation
4 O O of
4 O U-GPE Crm
4 O O software
4 O O and
4 O O handling
4 O O the
4 O O database
4 O B-PERSON Good
4 O L-PERSON Spoken
4 O O and
4 O O written
4 O U-LANGUAGE English

6 O O Having
6 O B-DATE 2.7
6 O L-DATE years
6 O O of
6 O O experience
6 O O in
6 O O Web
6 O O Application
6 O O design
6 O O using
6 O O python
6 O B-ORG Django
6 O L-ORG framework

6 O U-PRODUCT Highly
6 O O experienced
6 O O and
6 O O skilled
6 O B-LOC Agile
6 O L-LOC Developer
6 O O with
6 O O a
6 O O strong
6 O O record
6 O O of
6 O O excellent
6 O O teamwork
6 O O and
6 O O successful
6 O O coding
6 O O project
6 O O management

6 O O Performed
6 O O the
6 O O role
6 O O of
6 O O team
6 O O member
6 O O effectively

6 O O Extensively
6 O O worked
6 O O on
6 O O software
6 O O in
6 O O all
6 O O the
6 O O phases
6 O O including
6 O B-ORG Design
6 O L-ORG Development
6 O O Implementation
6 O U-ORG Integration
6 O O and
6 O U-GPE Testing

6 O U-PERSON Possesses
6 O O good
6 O O analytical
6 O O logical
6 O O ability
6 O O and
6 O O systematic
6 O O approach
6 O O to
6 O O problem
6 O O analysis
6 O O strong
6 O O debugging
6 O O and
6 O O troubleshooting
6 O O skills

6 O U-PERSON Working
6 O O on
6 O O classic
6 O O software
6 O O development
6 O O models
6 O O along
6 O B-LOC Agile
6 O L-LOC Methodologies

6 O O WORK
6 O O EXPERIENCE
6 B-Designation O Senior
6 I-Designation O System
6 I-Designation O Engineer
6 I-Designation O at
6 I-Designation O Infosys
6 L-Designation O Limited
6 O O Infosys
6 O B-DATE January
6 O L-DATE 2016
6 O O to
6 O O Present
6 O O training
6 O O program

6 O B-ORG Working
6 O I-ORG as
6 B-Designation I-ORG Senior
6 I-Designation I-ORG System
6 I-Designation L-ORG Engineer
6 I-Designation O at
6 I-Designation O Infosys
6 L-Designation O Limited
6 O O from
6 O B-DATE January
6 O L-DATE 2016
6 O O to
6 O O till
6 O O date

9 O B-ORG Manisha
9 O L-ORG Surve
9 B-Designation O Sales
9 I-Designation O Coordinator
9 L-Designation O rose
9 O O Trimos
9 O O Metrology
9 O B-ORG India
9 O I-ORG Pvt

9 O O Ltd
9 O O Thane
9 O B-ORG Maharashtra
9 O L-ORG Email
9 O O me
9 O O on
9 O O Indeed
9 O O indeed.com/r/Manisha-Surve/efc7fb79d544b62d
9 O O WORK
9 O O EXPERIENCE
9 B-Designation O Sales
9 I-Designation O Coordinator
9 L-Designation O rose
9 O U-ORG Trimos
9 O O Metrology
9 O U-GPE India
9 O O Pvt

9 O O Ltd
9 O O Thane
9 O B-ORG Maharashtra
9 O B-DATE November
9 O L-DATE 2006
9 O O to
9 O O Present
9 O O to
9 O O the
9 O O current
9 O O position
9 O O of
9 B-Designation B-ORG Manager
9 I-Designation I-ORG Customer
9 I-Designation I-ORG Support
9 I-Designation L-ORG Account
9 L-Designation O Assistant

9 B-Designation O Sr

9 I-Designation O Executive
9 I-Designation O Administration
9 I-Designation O Account
9 L-Designation O Assistant
9 O O One
9 O O Up
9 O O Marketing
9 O O Pvt

9 O O Ltd
9 O O Mumbai
9 O U-ORG Maharashtra
9 O B-DATE April
9 O I-DATE 2004
9 O I-DATE to
9 O I-DATE February
9 O L-DATE 2006
9 O O Sr

9 O O Executive
9 O O Administration
9 O O Accounts
9 O O Raj
9 O O International
9 O O Connections
9 O O Mumbai
9 O B-ORG Maharashtra
9 O B-DATE September
9 O I-DATE 2003
9 O I-DATE to
9 O I-DATE March
9 O L-DATE 2004
9 - B-ORG Computer
9 - I-ORG Operator
9 - L-ORG Team
9 - O leader
9 - O for
9 - O data
9 - O Entry
9 O O Dusk
9 O O Valley
9 O O Global
9 O O Service
9 O O Mumbai
9 O U-ORG Maharashtra
9 O B-DATE June
9 O L-DATE 2000
9 O O to
9 O B-DATE May
9 O L-DATE 2002
9 O O Worked
9 O O with
9 O B-ORG Ganesh
9 O L-ORG Brothers

9 O U-ORG Thane

9 O U-PERSON Worked
9 O O as
9 B-Designation B-ORG Computer
9 I-Designation I-ORG Operator
9 I-Designation I-ORG Front
9 I-Designation I-ORG Desk
9 L-Designation L-ORG Operation

9 O B-ORG AREA
9 O I-ORG OF
9 O I-ORG EXPERTISE
9 O I-ORG JOB
9 O L-ORG RESPOSIBILITIES

9 O B-ORG Service
9 O I-ORG Sales
9 O L-ORG Coordination

9 O B-ORG All
9 O I-ORG India
9 O I-ORG Online
9 O I-ORG CRM
9 O L-ORG Support
9 O O to
9 O O Regional
9 O O Back
9 O O Offices
9 O O Marketing
9 O O persons

9 O B-ORG Overall
9 O I-ORG Service
9 O L-ORG Orders
9 O O execution
9 O O from
9 O O purchase
9 O O order
9 O O to
9 O O deliveries
9 O O including
9 O B-ORG Invoice
9 O O generation

9 O O Ensuring
9 O O the
9 O O timely
9 O O qualitative
9 O O dispatch
9 O O of
9 O O goods
9 O O through
9 O O regular
9 O O intra
9 O O department
9 O O coordination
9 O O and
9 O O keeping
9 O O customers
9 O O informed
9 O O about
9 O O the
9 O O status
9 O O of
9 O O their
9 O O orders

9 O B-ORG Communicating
9 O L-ORG updating
9 O B-ORG Service
9 O L-ORG Marketing
9 O O team
9 O O about
9 O O respective
9 O O key
9 O O accounts
9 O O and
9 O O provide
9 O O timely
9 O O information
9 O O on
9 O U-ORG Service
9 O O pending
9 O O order
9 O O status
9 O O dispatch
9 O O plan
9 O O which
9 O O helps
9 O O them
9 O O to
9 O O implement
9 O O service
9 O O strategy
9 O O achieving
9 O O the
9 O U-ORG Service
9 O O targets
9 O O and
9 O O increasing
9 O O productivity
9 O O of
9 O O service

9 O O Collecting
9 O O analyzing
9 O O evaluating
9 O O and
9 O O accounting
9 O O the
9 O O key
9 O O service
9 O O figures
9 O O in
9 O O order
9 O O to
9 O O provide
9 O O the
9 O O correct
9 O O and
9 O O immediate
9 O O information
9 O O to
9 O B-ORG Senior
9 O L-ORG Management

9 O O https://www.indeed.com/r/Manisha-Surve/efc7fb79d544b62d?isid=rex-download&ikw=download-top&co=IN

9 O O Coordinating
9 O O with
9 O O National
9 O O Service
9 O O Head
9 O O regarding
9 O O network
9 O O and
9 O O promotional
9 O O events
9 O O to
9 O O develop
9 O O and
9 O O maintain
9 O O contact
9 O O with
9 O O potential
9 O O clients
9 O O and
9 O O professional
9 O O bodies

9 O O Maintaining
9 O O Stock
9 O O for
9 O U-ORG Warranty
9 O O material

9 O O Coordinating
9 O O with
9 O O Service
9 O O team
9 O I-ORG Account
9 O L-ORG Department
9 O O to
9 O O send
9 O O Invoice
9 O O against
9 O B-ORG New
9 O O orders

9 O B-ORG Prepare
9 O I-ORG Present
9 O I-ORG MIS
9 O L-ORG Reports
9 O B-ORG Cash
9 O L-ORG Flow
9 O O Updates
9 O O Weekly
9 O O to
9 O U-GPE MD

9 O O Account

9 O O Invoice
9 O O Generation
9 O O in
9 O O Tally

9 O B-GPE Debtors
9 O L-GPE Updates

9 O B-ORG Cash
9 O I-ORG Flow
9 O L-ORG Updates

9 O O Deferred
9 O O Income
9 O O details
9 O O of
9 O B-ORG Service
9 O I-ORG for
9 O L-ORG Finalization

9 O O Providing
9 O O Payment
9 O O details
9 O O to
9 O O release
9 O U-PERSON Documents

9 O U-PERSON Balance
9 O O confirmation
9 O O to
9 O O customers
9 O O as
9 O O per
9 O O company
9 O O Tally
9 O O records

9 O O All
9 O U-GPE India
9 O O Monthly
9 O O Salary
9 O O Link
9 O O Reports

9 O U-ORG MIS

9 O B-ORG Preparing
9 O O analyzing
9 O O various
9 O O reports
9 O O for
9 O U-ORG MIS
9 O O purpose
9 O O on
9 O U-GPE Yearly
9 O U-DATE Monthly
9 O U-PERSON Quarterly
9 O B-ORG Weekly
9 O I-ORG Dailybasis
9 O O providing
9 O O report
9 O O to
9 O B-ORG the
9 O I-ORG Management
9 O I-ORG Regional
9 O L-ORG Service
9 O O Head

9 O O Monitoring
9 O O the
9 O O trends
9 O O and
9 O O evaluating
9 O O the
9 O O performance
9 O O assessed
9 O O against
9 O U-DATE monthly
9 O O service
9 O O goals

9 O B-ORG Customer
9 O I-ORG Relationship
9 O L-ORG Management

9 O O Maintaining
9 O O a
9 O O healthy
9 O O relationship
9 O O with
9 O O existing
9 O O customers
9 O O while
9 O O opening
9 O O up
9 O O fresh
9 O O customers

9 O O Effective
9 O O management
9 O O and
9 O O resolutions
9 O O of
9 O O customer
9 O O queries
9 O O /complaints
9 O O with
9 O O the
9 O O help
9 O O of
9 O O engineers

9 O O Ensuring
9 O O the
9 O O highest
9 O O level
9 O O of
9 O O service
9 O O through
9 O O understanding/
9 O O identifying
9 O O customer
9 O O requirement
9 O O providing
9 O U-CARDINAL one
9 O O point
9 O O contact
9 O O for
9 O O same

9 O O Administrative
9 O O Support

9 O B-ORG Assisting
9 O I-ORG Managing
9 O I-ORG Director
9 O I-ORG Regional
9 O L-ORG Service
9 O O Head

9 O O Coordinating
9 O O and
9 O O responding
9 O O to
9 O O all
9 O O requests
9 O O of
9 O O internal
9 O O meetings

9 O B-ORG Office
9 O I-ORG Coordination
9 O I-ORG Vendor
9 O L-ORG Management

9 O O Providing
9 O O Training
9 O O to
9 O O the
9 O O new
9 O O existing
9 O U-ORG Team
9 O O members

9 O B-PERSON Supplier
9 O L-PERSON Co
9 O O ordination:-

9 O O Correspondence
9 O O with
9 O O Suppliers
9 O O for
9 O O Under
9 O O warranty

9 O O Technical
9 O O support
9 O O from
9 O O manufactures

9 O B-ORG Distribution
9 O I-ORG Process
9 O L-ORG Control

9 O B-ORG Physically
9 O I-ORG Oracle
9 O L-ORG ERP
9 O O systems

9 O B-ORG Hotel
9 O I-ORG Booking
9 O I-ORG Air
9 O I-ORG Road
9 O I-ORG Train
9 O L-ORG Booking

9 O B-PERSON Itinerary
9 O I-PERSON of
9 O I-PERSON Foreign
9 O L-PERSON Supplier
9 O O for
9 O O India
9 O O Visits

9 O O PROFESSIONAL
9 O O DEVELOPMENTS

9 O B-WORK_OF_ART Attended
9 O I-WORK_OF_ART Training
9 O I-WORK_OF_ART in
9 O L-WORK_OF_ART Reliance
9 O O for
9 O O software
9 O O in
9 O U-DATE 2006

9 O U-PERSON Attended
9 O O '
9 O O CRM
9 O O '
9 O O training
9 O O conducted
9 O O by
9 O U-ORG Team
9 O O for
9 O O modification
9 O O creation
9 O O documents
9 O O in
9 O O Software
9 O O in
9 O U-DATE 2009
9 O I-ORG 2011
9 O O coordinating
9 O O for
9 O B-ORG New
9 O I-ORG reporting

9 O B-WORK_OF_ART Attended
9 O I-WORK_OF_ART Training
9 O I-WORK_OF_ART for
9 O L-WORK_OF_ART Mass
9 O O mailing
9 O O through
9 O O software
9 O O in
9 O U-DATE 2011

9 O B-LOC Projects
9 O L-LOC Handled
9 O O in
9 O B-LOC Trimos
9 O L-LOC Metrology
9 O U-GPE India
9 O B-ORG Pvt

9 O O Ltd.

9 O B-PRODUCT New
9 O I-PRODUCT CRM
9 O I-PRODUCT Software
9 O L-PRODUCT Launch
9 O O [
9 O O The
9 O O project
9 O O was
9 O O In
9 O B-ORG CRM
9 O I-ORG Created
9 O I-ORG Documents
9 O O added
9 O O all
9 O O earlier
9 O O data
9 O O for
9 O O reporting
9 O O purpose
9 O O ]

9 O O Introduced
9 O O this
9 O O software
9 O O to
9 O O all
9 O B-ORG India
9 O L-ORG Back
9 O O office
9 O O sales-
9 O O Service
9 O O Staff

9 O B-ORG Sales
9 O L-ORG Service
9 O O Presently
9 O O Working
9 O O with
9 O B-ORG TRIMOS
9 O I-ORG METROLOGY
9 O I-ORG India
9 O I-ORG PVT

9 O O Ltd.
9 O O As
9 B-Designation O coordination
9 L-Designation B-ORG Manager
9 O I-ORG Customer
9 O L-ORG Support

9 O O CRM

9 O U-ORG MIS

9 O B-ORG All
9 O I-ORG India
9 O I-ORG Service
9 O L-ORG CRM
9 O O Coordinator
9 O O IT
9 O O SKILLS

9 O O Well
9 O O versed
9 O O with
9 O U-ORG Windows
9 O O MS
9 O O Office
9 O O Suite
9 O O Word
9 O O Excel
9 O B-ORG Power
9 O L-ORG Point
9 O O and
9 O O Internet
9 O O PERSONAL
9 O O DOSSIER
9 O O Communication
9 O O Address
9 O O [
9 O O …
9 O O ]
9 O B-PERSON Nandanvan
9 O L-PERSON Homes
9 O O Annex
9 O O I
9 O O Opp

9 O B-PERSON Reliance
9 O L-PERSON Market
9 O B-PERSON Parsik
9 O L-PERSON Nagar
9 O B-PERSON Kalwa
9 O L-PERSON W
9 O U-ORG Thane
9 O O 400
9 O O 605

10 O B-PERSON Hartej
10 O L-PERSON Kathuria
10 B-Designation B-ORG Data
10 I-Designation I-ORG Analyst
10 L-Designation I-ORG Intern
10 O I-ORG Oracle
10 O L-ORG Retail
10 O O Bengaluru
10 O B-PERSON Karnataka
10 O L-PERSON Email
10 O O me
10 O O on
10 O O Indeed
10 O O indeed.com/r/Hartej-Kathuria/04181c5962a4af19
10 O O Willing
10 O O to
10 O O relocate
10 O O to
10 O B-PERSON Delhi
10 O L-PERSON Bangalore
10 O B-ORG Karnataka
10 O L-ORG Gurgaon
10 O B-PERSON Haryana
10 O O WORK
10 O O EXPERIENCE
10 B-Designation O Data
10 I-Designation O Analyst
10 L-Designation O Intern
10 O O Oracle
10 O O Retail
10 O O Bengaluru
10 O U-GPE Karnataka
10 O B-DATE June
10 O L-DATE 2017
10 O O to
10 O O Present
10 O O Job
10 O O Responsibilities
10 O O o
10 O O As
10 O O an
10 O O intern
10 O O part
10 O O of
10 O O the
10 O B-ORG Global
10 O I-ORG Retail
10 O L-ORG Insights
10 O O team
10 O O at
10 O B-ORG Oracle
10 O L-ORG Retail
10 O O work
10 O O involved
10 O O creating
10 O O a
10 O O data
10 O O oriented
10 O O buisness
10 O O case
10 O O based
10 O O using
10 O O high
10 O O level
10 O O trends
10 O O for
10 O O various
10 O O retailers
10 O O using
10 O U-PRODUCT Excel
10 O O and
10 O U-ORG SQL

10 O O The
10 O O dataset
10 O O given
10 O O has
10 O U-CARDINAL 17
10 O O variables
10 O U-CARDINAL 12
10 O O nominal
10 O U-CARDINAL 2
10 O O ordinal
10 O O and
10 O U-CARDINAL 3
10 O O numerical

10 O O The
10 O O target
10 O O variable
10 O O has
10 O O value
10 O O true
10 O O if
10 O O the
10 O O patient
10 O O dies
10 O O within
10 O B-DATE one
10 O L-DATE year
10 O O of
10 O O the
10 O O operation
10 O O else
10 O O false
10 O O if
10 O O he
10 O O survives

10 O U-ORG Tool
10 O O used
10 O O R
10 O O https://www.indeed.com/r/Hartej-Kathuria/04181c5962a4af19?isid=rex-download&ikw=download-top&co=IN
10 O O Predict
10 O B-ORG the
10 O I-ORG Happiness
10 O I-ORG Sentimental
10 O L-ORG Analysis
10 O O The
10 O O objective
10 O O of
10 O O this
10 O O project
10 O O was
10 O O to
10 O O build
10 O O a
10 O O binary
10 O O classifcation
10 O O model
10 O O for
10 O O the
10 O O data
10 O O provided
10 O O by
10 O U-ORG TripAdvisor
10 O O consisiting
10 O O of
10 O O a
10 O O sample
10 O O of
10 O O hotel
10 O O reviews
10 O O provided
10 O O by
10 O O customers

10 O O The
10 O O model
10 O O built
10 O O can
10 O O be
10 O O used
10 O O by
10 O O them
10 O O to
10 O O understand
10 O O the
10 O O hotels
10 O O listed
10 O O by
10 O O them

10 O O Tool
10 O O Used
10 O O R
10 O B-ORG Predict
10 O L-ORG Network
10 O O attacks
10 O O The
10 O O objective
10 O O of
10 O O this
10 O O project
10 O O was
10 O O to
10 O O build
10 O O a
10 O O multi
10 O O class
10 O O classification
10 O O model
10 O O to
10 O O predict
10 O O the
10 O O type
10 O O of
10 O O attack
10 O O for
10 O O an
10 O O internet
10 O O network
10 O O company
10 O O in
10 O U-GPE Japan
10 O O which
10 O O has
10 O O been
10 O O facing
10 O O huge
10 O O losses
10 O O due
10 O O to
10 O O malicious
10 O O server
10 O O attacks

10 O O The
10 O O train
10 O O dataset
10 O O has
10 O U-CARDINAL 18
10 O O numerical
10 O O features
10 O O and
10 O U-CARDINAL 23
10 O O categorical
10 O O features

10 O O The
10 O O target
10 O O variable
10 O O has
10 O U-CARDINAL three
10 O O classes

11 O B-PERSON Chinmoy
11 O L-PERSON Choubey
11 O O Senior
11 O O Manager
11 B-Designation O Zonal
11 I-Designation O Business
11 L-Designation O Manager
11 O O Eko
11 O B-ORG India
11 O I-ORG Financial
11 O L-ORG Services
11 O U-PERSON Pvt

11 O O Ltd
11 O U-GPE Mumbai
11 O B-ORG Maharashtra
11 O L-ORG Email
11 O O me
11 O O on
11 O O Indeed
11 O O indeed.com
11 O O r
11 O O Chinmoy-
11 O U-ORG Choubey/6269f13a50009359
11 O O A
11 O O result
11 O O oriented
11 O O professional
11 O O offering
11 O B-DATE nearly
11 O I-DATE 13
11 O L-DATE years
11 O O of
11 O O a
11 O O successful
11 O O career
11 O O in
11 O O ~
11 O O Sales
11 O O and
11 O O Marketing
11 O O ~
11 O O Channel
11 O O Sales
11 O O Distribution
11 O O ~
11 O O Market
11 O O Analysis
11 O O ~
11 O O Strategy
11 O O Planning
11 O O ~
11 O O Client
11 O O Relationship
11 O O Management
11 O O ~
11 O B-ORG MIS
11 O I-ORG Reporting
11 O O ~
11 O O Cross
11 O O Functional
11 O O Coordination
11 O O ~
11 O O Performance
11 O O Management
11 O O ~
11 O B-ORG ATL
11 O L-ORG BTL
11 O O Activities

11 O O Led
11 O O business
11 O O planning
11 O O and
11 O O performance
11 O O management
11 O O of
11 O O channel
11 O O partners
11 O O including
11 O O development
11 O O and
11 O O execution
11 O O of
11 O O joint
11 O O sales
11 O O plans
11 O O local
11 O O area
11 O O marketing
11 O O staff
11 O O coaching
11 O O recruitment
11 O O and
11 O O hosting
11 O O constructive
11 O O meetings

11 O O Efficient
11 O O in
11 O O managing
11 O O the
11 O O channel
11 O O partner
11 O O programme
11 O O with
11 O O a
11 O O team
11 O O of
11 O O Dealers
11 O O Distributors
11 O O and
11 O B-ORG Value
11 O I-ORG Added
11 O L-ORG Resellers
11 O O ensured
11 O O accomplishment
11 O O of
11 O O overall
11 O O revenue
11 O O profit
11 O O targets
11 O O in
11 O O the
11 O O assigned
11 O O region

11 O O Allocated
11 O O budgets
11 O O to
11 O O support
11 O O channel
11 O O partner
11 O O programs
11 O O identified
11 O O and
11 O O nurtured
11 O O key
11 O O solution
11 O O providers
11 O O for
11 O O leveraging
11 O O channel
11 O O strategy

11 O O Helped
11 O O the
11 O O distributor
11 O O to
11 O O view
11 O O business
11 O O strategically
11 O O and
11 O O make
11 O O them
11 O O adopt
11 O O company
11 O O vision
11 O O of
11 O O brand
11 O O building

11 O O Managed
11 O O launch
11 O O of
11 O O a
11 O O new
11 O O product
11 O B-ORG ICICI
11 O I-ORG NEFT
11 O L-ORG IMPS
11 O B-ORG BC
11 O L-ORG Model
11 O O including
11 O O product
11 O O development
11 O O positioning
11 O O pricing
11 O O packaging
11 O O design
11 O O media
11 O O consumer
11 O O promotions
11 O O account
11 O O sell
11 O O in
11 O O and
11 O O retailer
11 O O activation

11 O U-PERSON Worked
11 O O closely
11 O O with
11 O B-ORG Customer
11 O I-ORG Service
11 O L-ORG Representatives
11 O O to
11 O O ensure
11 O O customer
11 O O satisfaction
11 O O and
11 O O problem
11 O O resolution

11 O O Leveraged
11 O O all
11 O O Below
11 O O The
11 O O Line
11 O O marketing
11 O O campaigns
11 O O by
11 O O designing
11 O O tools
11 O O and
11 O O programs
11 O O for
11 O O engaging
11 O O with
11 O O consumers
11 O O to
11 O O drive
11 O O customer
11 O O acquisition
11 O O and
11 O O transactions

11 O U-ORG Team
11 O O based
11 O O management
11 O O style
11 O O coupled
11 O O with
11 O O the
11 O O zeal
11 O O to
11 O O drive
11 O O visions
11 O O into
11 O O reality
11 O O Willing
11 O O to
11 O O relocate
11 O O Anywhere
11 O O WORK
11 O O EXPERIENCE
11 O O Senior
11 O O Manager
11 B-Designation O Zonal
11 I-Designation O Business
11 L-Designation O Manager
11 O O Eko
11 O O India
11 O O Financial
11 O O Services
11 O O Pvt

11 O O Managing
11 O O channel
11 O O sales
11 O O distribution
11 O O with
11 O O a
11 O O pin
11 O O point
11 O O focus
11 O O on
11 O O P&L
11 O O sheet

11 O O Mapping
11 O O target
11 O O market
11 O O layout
11 O O formats
11 O O for
11 O O new
11 O O initiatives
11 O O new
11 O O product
11 O O launches

11 O O Promoting
11 O O sales
11 O O working
11 O O on
11 O O P&L
11 O O of
11 O O the
11 O O activity
11 O O for
11 O O the
11 O O allocated
11 O O area

11 O O Assigning
11 O U-DATE monthly
11 O O target
11 O O to
11 O O team
11 O O members
11 O O retailers

11 O O Involving
11 O O in
11 O O product
11 O O presentation
11 O O providing
11 O O training
11 O O to
11 O O team
11 O O as
11 O O and
11 O O when
11 O O required

11 O O Managing
11 O O relations
11 O O with
11 O O partner
11 O U-ORG Bank
11 O O local
11 O O branches

11 O O Coordinating
11 O U-DATE daily
11 O U-ORG MIS
11 O O and
11 O O reporting
11 O O on
11 O O excel
11 O O and
11 O B-ORG PPT
11 O O https://www.indeed.com/r/Chinmoy-Choubey/6269f13a50009359?isid=rex-download&ikw=download-top&co=IN
11 O O https://www.indeed.com/r/Chinmoy-Choubey/6269f13a50009359?isid=rex-download&ikw=download-top&co=IN

11 O O Performing
11 O O periodic
11 O O market
11 O O and
11 O O program
11 O O analysis
11 O O of
11 O O targeted
11 O O customers
11 O O and
11 O O channel
11 O O partners

11 O O Optimizing
11 O O channel
11 O O functions
11 O O flows
11 O O direct
11 O O indirect
11 O O channel
11 O O partner
11 O O counter-
11 O O wise
11 O O targeting
11 O O all
11 O U-DATE monthly
11 O O channel
11 O O partner
11 O O incentives
11 O O payouts
11 O U-ORG BTL
11 O O schemes
11 O O promotions
11 O O primary
11 O O secondary
11 O O reporting
11 O O systems
11 O O and
11 O O process
11 O O automations

11 O O Collaborating
11 O O with
11 O O sales
11 O O product
11 O O development
11 O O and
11 O O solution
11 O O engineers
11 O O to
11 O O develop
11 O O strategic
11 O O sales
11 O O initiatives

11 O O Preparing
11 O O MIS
11 O O reports
11 O O required
11 O O by
11 O O management
11 O O on
11 O O inventory
11 O O holding
11 O U-DATE monthly
11 O O reports
11 O O tracking
11 O O of
11 O O spares
11 O O pending
11 O O and
11 O O executed
11 O O demands
11 O O analysis
11 O O consumption
11 O O of
11 O O spares
11 O O routinely

11 O O Highlights

11 O U-PERSON Worked
11 O O closely
11 O O with
11 O O channel
11 O O partners
11 O O to
11 O O generate
11 O O new
11 O O business
11 O O in
11 O O existing
11 O O accounts
11 O O and
11 O O in
11 O O new
11 O O markets
11 O O like
11 O U-GPE Mumbai
11 O U-GPE Punjab
11 O O and
11 O U-GPE Jharkhand

11 O O Recognized
11 O O for
11 O O exceeding
11 O O targets
11 O B-DATE month
11 O L-DATE month
11 O O with
11 O O cumulative
11 O O growth
11 O O of
11 O B-PERCENT 150
11 O L-PERCENT %
11 O U-DATE year
11 O O on
11 O U-DATE year
11 B-Designation O Assistant
11 L-Designation O Manager
11 O O Sales
11 O B-ORG Videocon
11 O I-ORG Industries
11 O L-ORG Ltd
11 O U-FAC Surat
11 O B-FAC Gujarat
11 O B-DATE March
11 O L-DATE 2009
11 O O to
11 O B-DATE May
11 O L-DATE 2010
11 O B-PERSON Brand
11 O L-PERSON Manager-
11 O O Kelvinator
11 O U-GPE Kenstar
11 O O and
11 O U-GPE Akai
11 O O In
11 O O charge
11 O U-NORP Surat
11 O B-GPE South
11 O L-GPE Gujarat
11 O B-ORG Daman
11 O L-ORG Silvasa
11 O O Key
11 O O Result
11 O O Areas

11 O U-PERSON Supervised
11 O O brands
11 O O such
11 O O as
11 O B-ORG Kelvinator
11 O I-ORG Kenstar
11 O L-ORG Akai
11 O O which
11 O O comprised
11 O O of
11 O O all
11 O O categories
11 O O LCD
11 O U-ORG CTV
11 O U-ORG Refrigerator
11 O B-ORG Washing
11 O L-ORG Machine
11 O B-ORG AC
11 O L-ORG SHA

11 O O Managed
11 O O overall
11 O O business
11 O B-ORG Sales
11 O L-ORG Collections
11 O O by
11 O O assigning
11 O U-DATE monthly
11 O O targets
11 O O to
11 O O a
11 O O team
11 O O of
11 O O sales
11 O O executives
11 O O direct
11 O O dealers
11 O O in
11 O O shop
11 O O demonstrators
11 O O in
11 O O the
11 O O assigned
11 O O area
11 O O retail
11 O O format

11 O U-PERSON Rolled
11 O O out
11 O O various
11 O O new
11 O O products
11 O O and
11 O O conducted
11 O O successful
11 O O launches

11 O O Started
11 O O new
11 O O retail
11 O O formats
11 O O DIGI
11 O O World

11 O O Monitored
11 O O the
11 O O overall
11 O O operations
11 O O of
11 O O the
11 O O retail
11 O O format
11 B-Designation B-PERSON Zonal
11 I-Designation L-PERSON Lead
11 I-Designation O Manager
11 O O PCO
11 O O Sales
11 O B-ORG Reliance
11 O I-ORG Communications
11 O I-ORG Ltd
11 O L-ORG Rajkot
11 O O Gujarat
11 O B-DATE July
11 O I-DATE 2008
11 O I-DATE to
11 O I-DATE March
11 O L-DATE 2009
11 O O In
11 O O charge
11 O U-PERSON Saurasthra
11 O O Gujarat
11 O O Customer
11 O O Executive
11 O B-FAC PepsiCo
11 O I-FAC India
11 O L-FAC Sonipat
11 O B-PERSON Haryana
11 O B-DATE January
11 O I-DATE 2007
11 O I-DATE to
11 O I-DATE July
11 O L-DATE 2008
11 B-Designation O Territory
11 I-Designation O Sales
11 I-Designation O In
11 L-Designation O charge
11 O O Pidilite
11 O O Industries
11 O O Ltd
11 O O Gurgaon
11 O B-PERSON Haryana
11 O B-DATE February
11 O I-DATE 2004
11 O I-DATE to
11 O I-DATE January
11 O L-DATE 2007
11 B-Designation O Officer
11 L-Designation O Sales
11 O B-PERSON Choksey
11 O I-PERSON Chemicals
11 O L-PERSON Pvt

11 O O Ltd
11 O B-GPE New
11 O L-GPE Delhi
11 O U-GPE Delhi
11 O B-DATE October
11 O L-DATE 2002
11 O O to
11 O B-DATE February
11 O L-DATE 2004
11 O U-ORG EDUCATION
11 O O NIIT
11 O U-DATE 2015
11 U-Degree O MBA
11 O O in
11 O B-ORG Marketing
11 "B-College Name" I-ORG University
11 "I-College Name" I-ORG of
11 "L-College Name" L-ORG Pune
11 O O Pune
11 O U-ORG Maharashtra
11 O U-DATE 2002
11 U-Degree U-GPE B.Sc

11 "B-College Name" B-ORG Ram
11 "I-College Name" I-ORG Krishna
11 "I-College Name" I-ORG Dwarika
11 "L-College Name" L-ORG College
11 O B-ORG Magadh
11 O L-ORG University
11 O U-DATE 1997
11 O O ADDITIONAL
11 O O INFORMATION
11 O O IT
11 O O SKILLS

11 O B-ORG MS
11 O L-ORG Office

11 O O Internet
11 O O Applications

12 O O ❖
12 O O A
12 O O keen
12 O O analyst
12 O O skilled
12 O O in
12 O O market
12 O O sales
12 O O forecasting
12 O O identifying
12 O O formulating
12 O O strategies
12 O O to
12 O O exploit
12 O O business
12 O O opportunities

12 O O Well
12 O O versed
12 O O in
12 O O building
12 O O new
12 O O territories
12 O O expanding
12 O O opportunities
12 O O within
12 O O existing
12 O O client
12 O O base

12 O O ❖
12 O O Strategic
12 O O Planning
12 O B-ORG Business
12 O I-ORG Development
12 O I-ORG Sales
12 O I-ORG Marketing
12 O I-ORG Customer
12 O L-ORG Service
12 O O Client
12 O O Servicing
12 O O WORK
12 O O EXPERIENCE
12 B-Designation O Sales
12 L-Designation O Manager
12 O U-ORG IAL
12 O O Emirates
12 O O Logistics
12 O O LLC
12 O B-PERSON Jebel
12 O I-PERSON Ali
12 O B-DATE March
12 O L-DATE 2018
12 O O to
12 O B-ORG Present
12 O I-ORG Company
12 O I-ORG Profile
12 O O Freight
12 O O Forwarding
12 O O and
12 O U-ORG Logistics
12 O O ❖
12 O O Handling
12 O O keys
12 O O accounts
12 O O clients
12 O O across
12 O U-ORG GCC
12 O O ❖
12 O O Handling
12 O O Team
12 O O of
12 O O Business
12 O O Development
12 O O Managers
12 O B-ORG Sales
12 O L-ORG Executive
12 O O and
12 O O Sales
12 O O coordinator
12 O O ❖
12 O O Major
12 O O clients
12 O O for
12 O B-ORG Air
12 O L-ORG Freight
12 O O and
12 O O Express
12 O O Mode
12 O O ❖
12 O O Handling
12 O O some
12 O O of
12 O B-ORG the
12 O I-ORG Top
12 O L-ORG Brands
12 O O of
12 O O GCC
12 O O for
12 O U-ORG Fashion
12 O U-ORG Automotive
12 O B-ORG Heavy
12 O L-ORG Engineering
12 O U-ORG Spare
12 O O parts
12 O O ❖
12 O O Developed
12 O O the
12 O O Trade
12 O O lane
12 O O for
12 O B-ORG Export
12 O I-ORG and
12 O L-ORG Import
12 O O shipments
12 O O for
12 O U-ORG GCC
12 O O and
12 O U-LOC Africa
12 O O ❖
12 O O Currently
12 O O handling
12 O U-ORG Import
12 O O shipments
12 O O on
12 O O express
12 O O lane
12 O O from
12 O U-LOC Europe
12 O B-LOC Far
12 O L-LOC East
12 O O and
12 O B-LOC South
12 O I-LOC East
12 O L-LOC Asia
12 O O ❖
12 O U-DATE Monthly
12 O O volume
12 O O on
12 O B-ORG Air
12 O L-ORG Freight
12 O O and
12 O O express
12 O O lane
12 O O approximate
12 O O around
12 O O 35-
12 O O 40
12 O O Ton
12 O O on
12 O O express
12 O O and
12 O O air
12 O O freight
12 O O mode
12 O O ❖
12 O O Land
12 O O freight
12 O U-ORG LTL
12 O O movement
12 O O for
12 O O GCC
12 O O region
12 O O approx

12 O O volume
12 O O around
12 O B-QUANTITY 10=
12 O I-QUANTITY 15
12 O L-QUANTITY ton
12 O O every
12 O O week
12 O O Handled
12 O O few
12 O O government
12 O O projects
12 O O in
12 O B-ORG GCC
12 O I-ORG Region
12 O I-ORG for
12 O I-ORG Medical
12 O I-ORG Equipment
12 O O ❖
12 O O Handling
12 O O Team
12 O O of
12 O O Business
12 O O Development
12 O O Managers
12 O O Sales
12 O O Executive
12 O O and
12 O O Sales
12 O O coordinator
12 O O ❖
12 O O Set
12 O O up
12 O O console
12 O O service
12 O O from
12 O B-LOC Far
12 O L-LOC East
12 O B-LOC South
12 O I-LOC East
12 O L-LOC Asia
12 O U-LOC Europe
12 O O and
12 O U-GPE USA
12 O O for
12 O B-ORG Air
12 O L-ORG Freight
12 O O ❖
12 O O Achieving
12 O O own
12 O O target
12 O O and
12 O U-ORG Team
12 O O target
12 O O ❖
12 O O Handling
12 O O some
12 O O of
12 O O the
12 O O well
12 O O know
12 O O Multinational
12 O O Clients
12 O O from
12 O U-ORG UAE
12 O O and
12 O B-PERSON Euro
12 O O https://www.indeed.com/r/Rafique-Kazi/b646d13929e74f07?isid=rex-download&ikw=download-top&co=IN
12 O O ❖
12 O O Currently
12 O O Looking
12 O O after
12 O O a
12 O O revenue
12 O O 1-
12 O B-CARDINAL 1.5
12 O L-CARDINAL million
12 O O AED
12 O O with
12 O O a
12 O O profitability
12 O O of
12 O B-PERCENT 15-
12 O I-PERCENT 18
12 O L-PERCENT percent
12 O O every
12 O O month
12 O O ❖
12 O O Adding
12 O O new
12 O O business
12 O B-DATE every
12 O L-DATE month
12 O O to
12 O O increase
12 O O profitability
12 O O ❖
12 O O Negotiating
12 O O with
12 O O the
12 O O agents
12 O O and
12 O O airlines
12 O O to
12 O O get
12 O O appropriate
12 O O quote
12 O O for
12 O O huge
12 O O volumes
12 O O ❖
12 O O Maintaining
12 O O team
12 O O statistics
12 O O so
12 O O that
12 O O the
12 O O profitability
12 O O is
12 O O increased
12 O B-ORG ❖
12 O I-ORG Promoting
12 O I-ORG Sea
12 O I-ORG and
12 O I-ORG Land
12 O L-ORG Freight
12 O O department
12 O O with
12 O O new
12 O O leads
12 O O for
12 O U-ORG LCL
12 O U-ORG FCL
12 O O movements
12 O O ❖
12 O O Strategic
12 O O planning
12 O O with
12 O B-PERSON Sales
12 O L-PERSON Team
12 O O to
12 O O ease
12 O O the
12 O O process
12 O O of
12 O O achieving
12 O U-DATE quarterly
12 O O targets
12 O O ❖
12 O O Promoting
12 O O Consol
12 O O Service
12 O O to
12 O O the
12 O O clients
12 O O to
12 O O increase
12 O O the
12 O O profitability
12 O O with
12 O O the
12 O B-ORG Clients
12 B-Designation L-ORG Sales
12 L-Designation O Manager
12 O U-ORG Syon
12 O B-PERSON Logistics
12 O I-PERSON LLC
12 O O Dubai
12 O B-DATE May
12 O I-DATE 2015
12 O I-DATE to
12 O I-DATE January
12 O L-DATE 2018
12 O O Company
12 O O Profile
12 O O Freight
12 O O Forwarding
12 O O Responsibilities
12 O O ❖
12 O O Handling
12 O O accounts
12 O O for
12 O O air
12 O O and
12 O O sea
12 O O freight
12 O O clients
12 O O ❖
12 O O Trade
12 O O lane
12 O O from
12 O B-LOC South
12 O L-LOC East
12 O O and
12 O O far
12 O B-LOC East
12 O L-LOC Asia
12 O O ❖
12 O O Negotiation
12 O O with
12 O O the
12 O O agents
12 O O and
12 O O vendors
12 O O for
12 O U-LOC Europe
12 O O and
12 O U-ORG GCC
12 O O movement
12 O O via
12 O O land
12 O O and
12 O O sea
12 O O ❖
12 O O Express
12 O O lane
12 O O set
12 O O via
12 O O from
12 O U-LOC Europe
12 O O and
12 O U-GPE USA
12 O O ❖
12 O B-ORG Sea
12 O L-ORG Freight
12 O O LCL
12 O O movement
12 O O from
12 O U-GPE Germany
12 O O and
12 O U-GPE China
12 O O ❖
12 O O Handling
12 O O Top
12 O O Key
12 O O Accounts
12 O O in
12 O U-GPE UAE
12 O O for
12 O O air
12 O O and
12 O O sea
12 O U-PERSON Freight
12 O O ❖
12 O O Major
12 O O Volume
12 O O from
12 O B-ORG FMCG
12 O L-ORG Companies
12 O O manufacturer
12 O O and
12 O U-ORG Trader
12 O O in
12 O O GCC
12 O O Region
12 O O ❖
12 O O Cross
12 O O trade
12 O O from
12 O O China-
12 O O Central
12 O O and
12 O B-GPE East
12 O L-GPE Africa
12 B-Designation O Sales
12 L-Designation O Manager
12 O B-ORG Compex
12 O L-ORG International
12 O O Logistics
12 O O LLC
12 O O Dubai
12 O B-DATE December
12 O I-DATE 2010
12 O I-DATE to
12 O I-DATE November
12 O L-DATE 2015
12 O O Company
12 O O Profile
12 O O Freight
12 O O Forwarding
12 O B-ORG Cargo
12 O I-ORG and
12 O I-ORG Logistics
12 O L-ORG Company
12 O O Responsibilities
12 O O ❖
12 O O Preparing
12 O O of
12 O O service
12 O O agreement
12 O O and
12 O O submitting
12 O O it
12 O O to
12 O O co
12 O O or
12 O O prate
12 O O clients
12 O O Coordinating
12 O O with
12 O O the
12 O O clients
12 O O by
12 O O offering
12 O O them
12 O O best
12 O O quote
12 O O ❖
12 O O Selling
12 O O of
12 O O the
12 O O major
12 O O products
12 O O and
12 O O services
12 O O offered
12 O O by
12 O O the
12 O O company
12 O O to
12 O O the
12 O O client
12 O U-ORG Air
12 O O -Freight
12 O O Sea
12 O O -Freight
12 O B-ORG Land
12 O L-ORG Freight
12 O O and
12 O B-ORG Courier
12 O L-ORG Services

12 O O ❖
12 O O Educating
12 O O the
12 O O external
12 O O and
12 O O internal
12 O O customers
12 O O about
12 O O the
12 O O policy
12 O O and
12 O O procedure
12 O O about
12 O O custom
12 O O clearance

12 O O ❖
12 O O Currently
12 O O looking
12 O O after
12 O U-CARDINAL 70
12 O O co
12 O O operate
12 O O clients
12 O O ❖
12 O O Achieving
12 O U-CARDINAL four
12 O O sign
12 O O ups
12 O O of
12 O O account
12 O O in
12 O O every
12 O O week
12 O O ❖
12 O O Coordinating
12 O O with
12 O O management
12 O O and
12 O O keeping
12 O O them
12 O O posted
12 O O about
12 O O the
12 O O sales
12 O O strategy
12 O O ❖
12 O O Develop
12 O O sales
12 O O recovery
12 O O report
12 O O journey
12 O O cycle
12 O O and
12 O O provide
12 O U-DATE daily
12 O O sales
12 O O report
12 O O to
12 O O the
12 O O sales
12 O O manager

12 O O ❖
12 O O Negotiating
12 O O with
12 O O the
12 O O service
12 O O provider
12 O O in
12 O O regards
12 O O to
12 O O quote
12 O O provided
12 O O to
12 O O the
12 O O company
12 O O ❖
12 O O Maintaining
12 O O business
12 O O with
12 O O high
12 O O profit
12 O O margin

12 O O Field
12 O O Sales
12 O O Executive
12 O U-GPE Dubai
12 O B-DATE April
12 O I-DATE 2008
12 O I-DATE to
12 O I-DATE December
12 O L-DATE 2010
12 O O Company
12 O O Profile
12 O O Express
12 O O and
12 O U-PERSON Courier
12 O O service
12 O O Responsibilities
12 O O ❖

12 O B-ORG Achieve
12 O L-ORG Targets
12 O O and
12 O O acquire
12 O B-CARDINAL 8
12 O L-CARDINAL 9
12 O O new
12 O O accounts
12 O O every
12 O O month
12 O O ❖
12 O O Looking
12 O O after
12 O U-ORG Territory
12 O O comprising
12 O O of
12 O U-ORG DAFZA
12 O B-ORG Deira
12 O L-ORG Bur
12 O U-GPE Ghusais
12 O B-PERSON Garhoud
12 O O ❖
12 O O Looking
12 O O after
12 O O the
12 O O business
12 O O around
12 O O 150
12 O U-CARDINAL thousand
12 O U-ORG AED
12 O O every
12 O O month
12 O O ❖
12 O O Selling
12 O O of
12 O O the
12 O O major
12 O O products
12 O O and
12 O O services
12 O O offered
12 O O by
12 O O the
12 O O company
12 O O to
12 O O the
12 O O client
12 O O Air
12 O O -Freight
12 O O Sea
12 O O -Freight
12 O B-PERSON Land
12 O L-PERSON Freight
12 O O ❖
12 O O Submitting
12 O O Weekly
12 O O and
12 O U-DATE Monthly
12 O O reports
12 O O to
12 B-Designation O Sales
12 L-Designation O Manager
12 B-Designation O Senior
12 I-Designation O Sales
12 I-Designation O and
12 I-Designation B-ORG Customer
12 I-Designation L-ORG Service
12 L-Designation O Executive
12 O B-ORG Emirates
12 O I-ORG NBD
12 O L-ORG Bank
12 O O Dubai
12 O B-DATE September
12 O I-DATE 2006
12 O I-DATE to
12 O I-DATE January
12 O L-DATE 2008
12 O O Company
12 O O Profile
12 O U-CARDINAL One
12 O O of
12 O B-ORG the
12 O I-ORG Leading
12 O L-ORG Banks
12 O O in
12 O B-LOC Gulf
12 O L-LOC Sector
12 O O Responsibilities
12 O O To
12 O O sell
12 O O multiple
12 O U-ORG Products
12 O O to
12 O O the
12 O O customers
12 O O based
12 O O on
12 O O the
12 O O client
12 O O requirements
12 O O and
12 O O to
12 O O increase
12 O O Profits

12 O O Responsible
12 O O for
12 O O compliance
12 O O and
12 O O adherence
12 O O to
12 O O policies
12 O O Set
12 O O up
12 O O processes
12 O O systems
12 O O and
12 O O controls
12 O O to
12 O O manage
12 O O customer
12 O O relationships

12 O U-PERSON Develop
12 O O and
12 O O implement
12 O O strategy
12 O O for
12 O O Increasing
12 O O Revenues
12 O O for
12 O O the
12 O O division

12 O O Responsible
12 O O for
12 O O the
12 O O Top
12 O O end
12 O O clients
12 O O of
12 O O the
12 O O branch
12 O O and
12 O O to
12 O O retain
12 O O them

12 O U-ORG Coordinate
12 O O with
12 O O other
12 O O group
12 O O companies
12 O O to
12 O O synergies
12 O O business

12 O B-ORG Business
12 O I-ORG Development
12 O L-ORG Expansion
